

# DESIREE SOLOMON WEB DEVELOPER

Orlando, Florida 917-664-3989 d.d.solomon4@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm an aspiring Junior Web Developer with over 15 years of Hospitality and Customer Service experience. I have a Bachelor's Degree from Monroe College in Hospitality Management, and a Certification from the University of Central Florida in Full Stack Web Development. I'm looking to work for a company that encourages teamwork and growth.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**HILTON ORLANDO, 2014 - PRESENT** 

Bartender

**HILTON ORLANDO, 2016 - 2017** 

**Bar Supervisor** 

**HAKKASAN NYC, 2012-2014** 

Server

#### **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

**MONROE COLLEGE** 

**BBS** in Hospitality Management

## **SKILLS**

**REACT.JS** 

**MYSQL** 

NODE

**EXPRESS** 

**JAVASCRIPT** 

**HTML** 

CSS

**BOOTSTRAP** 

### **REFERENCES**

**AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST** 

